<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Bestand><titel>Rangers vs. Canadiens Game 4: On playing with leads, and closing out</titel><afbeelding>file:///C:/Users/Student/Documents/Visual Studio 2012/Projects/BlogCase/BlogCase/HTML/images/sample5.jpg</afbeelding><RTB>&lt;Section xmlns="http://schemas.microsoft.com/winfx/2006/xaml/presentation" xml:space="preserve" TextAlignment="Left" LineHeight="Auto" IsHyphenationEnabled="False" xml:lang="en-us" FlowDirection="LeftToRight" NumberSubstitution.CultureSource="Text" NumberSubstitution.Substitution="AsCulture" FontFamily="Segoe UI" FontStyle="Normal" FontWeight="Normal" FontStretch="Normal" FontSize="12" Foreground="#FF000000" Typography.StandardLigatures="True" Typography.ContextualLigatures="True" Typography.DiscretionaryLigatures="False" Typography.HistoricalLigatures="False" Typography.AnnotationAlternates="0" Typography.ContextualAlternates="True" Typography.HistoricalForms="False" Typography.Kerning="True" Typography.CapitalSpacing="False" Typography.CaseSensitiveForms="False" Typography.StylisticSet1="False" Typography.StylisticSet2="False" Typography.StylisticSet3="False" Typography.StylisticSet4="False" Typography.StylisticSet5="False" Typography.StylisticSet6="False" Typography.StylisticSet7="False" Typography.StylisticSet8="False" Typography.StylisticSet9="False" Typography.StylisticSet10="False" Typography.StylisticSet11="False" Typography.StylisticSet12="False" Typography.StylisticSet13="False" Typography.StylisticSet14="False" Typography.StylisticSet15="False" Typography.StylisticSet16="False" Typography.StylisticSet17="False" Typography.StylisticSet18="False" Typography.StylisticSet19="False" Typography.StylisticSet20="False" Typography.Fraction="Normal" Typography.SlashedZero="False" Typography.MathematicalGreek="False" Typography.EastAsianExpertForms="False" Typography.Variants="Normal" Typography.Capitals="Normal" Typography.NumeralStyle="Normal" Typography.NumeralAlignment="Normal" Typography.EastAsianWidths="Normal" Typography.EastAsianLanguage="Normal" Typography.StandardSwashes="0" Typography.ContextualSwashes="0" Typography.StylisticAlternates="0"&gt;&lt;Paragraph&gt;&lt;Run xml:lang="nl-nl"&gt;The Rangers held three different leads Sunday night, while their last—even though it was the shortest lived—was the most important. Martin St. Louis' goal 6:04 into the first overtime session gave New York a 3-2 victory, and a 3-1 lead in their Eastern Conference Finals series again Montreal.&lt;/Run&gt;&lt;/Paragraph&gt;&lt;Paragraph&gt;&lt;Run xml:lang="nl-nl"&gt;&lt;/Run&gt;&lt;/Paragraph&gt;&lt;Paragraph&gt;&lt;Run xml:lang="nl-nl"&gt;The Rangers are now 10-3 in the postseason in games in which they've scored first, while they improved to 9-0 when leading after two periods. For the second time all postseason, the Blueshirts hold a two-game edge in a series.&lt;/Run&gt;&lt;/Paragraph&gt;&lt;Paragraph&gt;&lt;Run xml:lang="nl-nl"&gt;&lt;/Run&gt;&lt;/Paragraph&gt;&lt;Paragraph&gt;&lt;Run xml:lang="nl-nl"&gt;Montreal was able to climb back into Sunday night's game twice. First, a bad decision by Anton Stralman in the neutral zone sprung David Desharnais and Francis Bouillon on a 2-on-1 to knot the score at one. Then, the Rangers seventh penalty of the contest finally cost them, as a P.K. Subban blast got through Henrik Lundqvist to send the game into overtime.&lt;/Run&gt;&lt;/Paragraph&gt;&lt;Paragraph&gt;&lt;Run xml:lang="nl-nl"&gt;&lt;/Run&gt;&lt;/Paragraph&gt;&lt;Paragraph&gt;&lt;Run xml:lang="nl-nl"&gt;But in the end, St. Louis was able to sneak one over the glove of Dustin Tokarski and under the crossbar for the Game 4 victory. The Canadiens' comeback ultimately fell short, and, the Rangers protected a lead, not only on the scoreboard, but in the series.&lt;/Run&gt;&lt;/Paragraph&gt;&lt;Paragraph&gt;&lt;Run xml:lang="nl-nl"&gt;&lt;/Run&gt;&lt;/Paragraph&gt;&lt;Paragraph&gt;&lt;Run xml:lang="nl-nl"&gt;Momentum is a tricky thing when it comes to playoff hockey. Day-to-day, it doesn't really exist. The 7-2 thrashing the Rangers handed out in Game 1 was followed by a game in which they were outplayed. (Yes, they won that game, and again, it just goes back to how there's no rhyme of reason to hockey.)&lt;/Run&gt;&lt;/Paragraph&gt;&lt;Paragraph&gt;&lt;Run xml:lang="nl-nl"&gt;&lt;/Run&gt;&lt;/Paragraph&gt;&lt;Paragraph&gt;&lt;Run xml:lang="nl-nl"&gt;Which is precisely why, when the series shifted back to New York, with the Rangers up 2-0, Montreal rallied in Game 3 to turn it into a series. It was one of the three Rangers' losses all playoffs when New York struck first. The lead was not protected, while the Blueshirts still clung to an edge in the series.&lt;/Run&gt;&lt;/Paragraph&gt;&lt;Paragraph&gt;&lt;Run xml:lang="nl-nl"&gt;&lt;/Run&gt;&lt;/Paragraph&gt;&lt;Paragraph&gt;&lt;Run xml:lang="nl-nl"&gt;But if you're talking about momentum, or at least feeling the affects of a win in a seven-game series, look no further than Sunday night. Had the Rangers lost, they would have again, for the second straight game (both on their home ice), allowed Montreal to erase a deficit on the scoreboard to ultimately erase a deficit in the series.&lt;/Run&gt;&lt;/Paragraph&gt;&lt;Paragraph&gt;&lt;Run xml:lang="nl-nl"&gt;&lt;/Run&gt;&lt;/Paragraph&gt;&lt;Paragraph&gt;&lt;Run xml:lang="nl-nl"&gt;Demoralizing? Maybe not. But doubt-inducing? Potentially, sure.&lt;/Run&gt;&lt;/Paragraph&gt;&lt;Paragraph&gt;&lt;Run xml:lang="nl-nl"&gt;&lt;/Run&gt;&lt;/Paragraph&gt;&lt;Paragraph&gt;&lt;Run xml:lang="nl-nl"&gt;On the flip-side, it wasn't as much a demoralizing loss for Montreal as a reality check. Win three straight—two of which on home ice, where they've yet to beat the Rangers this series, and one in Madison Square Garden—or face elimination.&lt;/Run&gt;&lt;/Paragraph&gt;&lt;Paragraph&gt;&lt;Run xml:lang="nl-nl"&gt;&lt;/Run&gt;&lt;/Paragraph&gt;&lt;Paragraph&gt;&lt;Run xml:lang="nl-nl"&gt;The Canadiens were an overtime goal Sunday night from completely changing the dynamic of this series. Or if Alex Galchenyuk's wrister in the third had missed Lundqvist's stick, or rotated a bit differently as it hit the crossbar, and again, maybe it's a 2-2 tie heading back to the Bell Centre.&lt;/Run&gt;&lt;/Paragraph&gt;&lt;Paragraph&gt;&lt;Run xml:lang="nl-nl"&gt;&lt;/Run&gt;&lt;/Paragraph&gt;&lt;Paragraph&gt;&lt;Run xml:lang="nl-nl"&gt;Hockey is a game of bounces, and you need good ones to have any chance at winning a Cup. Meanwhile, the Rangers did what they needed to do when heading home with a 2-0 series lead: they protected it. Now, they have to win one of the next three to give themselves a chance at hockey's grandest prize.&lt;/Run&gt;&lt;/Paragraph&gt;&lt;/Section&gt;</RTB></Bestand>